Guide to the Arthur Brown Papers SC0707
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Additional Drawings, Accession ARCH-2006-256
  - Carnegie Institution Lab Basement Plan, 1928 Nov 26 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Carnegie Institution Lab First Floor Plan, 1928 Nov 26 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Carnegie Institution Lab Second Floor Plan, 1928 Nov 26 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Carnegie Institution Lab Basement Heating and Electric Wiring, 1926 Nov 26 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Carnegie Institution Lab 1st Story Heating and Electric Wiring, 1926 Nov 26 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Carnegie Institution Lab 2nd Story Heating and Electric Wiring, 1926 Nov 26 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Carnegie Institution Lab Flat Slab Details, 1928 Nov 26 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Carnegie Institution Lab Foundation Plan and Sections, 1928 Nov 26 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Floor B 4 or Basement of O.P.D., 1927 Dec 13 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Floor B 3 or Main Floor of O.P.D. General Plan, 1927 Dec 13 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Floor B 2 or 2nd Floor of O.P.D., 1927 Dec 13 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Floor B 1 or 3rd Floor of O.P.D., 1927 Dec 13 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Stanford Clinical Hospital Main Floor, 1927 Dec 13 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Stanford Clinical Hospital Male Medical Wards 2nd Floor, 1927 Dec 13 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Stanford Clinical Hospital Webster Street Elevation, 1927 Dec 13 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Blueprint: Alterations to Third Floor Lane Hospital, 1919 Nov 13 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Blueprint: Webster Street Elevation Lane Hospital (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Blueprint: Electring Wiring, Heating Plumbing Plans Lane Hospital, 1920 Jun 15 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Alterations to Third Floor Lane Hospital (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Webster Street Elevation Lane Hospital (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Alterations to Third Floor Floor Plan Lane Hospital (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Hoover Library on War Plot Plan, 1939 Aug 08 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Hoover Library on War Floor Plans First Basement, 1939 Aug 08 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Hoover Library on War Floor Plans 2nd, 12th, 13th, 14th, 15th 16th, 1939 Aug 08 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Hoover Library on War Floor Plans 3rd, 4th, 9th, 10th 11th, 1939 Aug 08 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Hoover Library on War North Elevation, 1939 Aug 08 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Hoover Library on War South Elevation, 1939 Aug 08 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Hoover Library on War West Elevation, 1939 Aug 08 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Hoover Library on War Section on L, 1939 Aug 08 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Hoover Library Main Entrance Details, 1939 Aug 08 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Hoover Library on War Spandrel Sects. 1st 12th Floors, 1939 Aug 08 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Hoover Library on War Exterior Details 14th Floor, 1939 Aug 08 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Hoover Library on War Dome Lantern, 1939 Aug 08 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Hoover Library on War 1st Floor Details Plans Elevations, 1939 Aug 08 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Hoover Library on War Details of Lobby Exhibition Room, 1939 Aug 08 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Hoover Library on War Book Stacks, 1939 Aug 08 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Hoover Library on War Special Trim 11th Floor, 1939 Aug 08 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Hoover Library on War Toilet Room Details, 1939 Aug 08 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Hoover Library on War Stair No.1 Stair Details (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Hoover Library on War Stair No. 2, 3 4 Stair Details (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Hoover Library on War Door Window Details (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Hoover Library on War Schedule of Finishes Detail of Lamp Standard (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Hoover Library on War Doorway metalGates Entrance Lobby (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Hoover Library on War Structural Steel Column Schedule, General Notes Typical Details, 1939 Oct 27 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Hoover Library on War Structural Steel First Floor Framing, 1939 Oct 27 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Hoover Library on War Structural Steel 2nd 3rd Floor and Cubicle Roof Framing, 1939 Oct 27 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Hoover Library on War Structural Steel 4th to 16th Floors Incl. Dome Deck Framing, 1939 Oct 27 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Hoover Library on War Structural Steel Bracing Diagram Details, 1939 Oct 27 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Hoover Library on War Structural Steel Bracing Diagram Details, 1939 Oct 28 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Hoover Library on War Foundation Plan, 1939 Oct 29 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Tower Footing Top Reinforcement, 1939 Oct 30 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Tower Footing Bottom Reinforcement, 1939 Oct 31 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Tower Footing Sections Details, 1939 Oct 32 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Concrete Details Sections 1 to 5 incl., 1939 Oct 33 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Concrete Details Sections 6 to 8 B incl., 1939 Oct 34 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Concrete Details Sections 9 to 13D incl., 1939 Oct 35 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Concrete Details Sections 14 to 17B, 1939 Oct 36 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Concrete Details Sections 18 to 25 incl., 1939 Oct 37 (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Concrete Details Sections 26 to 31 incl., 1939 Oct 38 (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Concrete Details Sections 32, 33, 1939 Oct 39 (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - Concrete Details Sections 34, 35, 1939 Oct 40 (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - Concrete Details Stair No.1, 1939 Oct 41 (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - General Notes Slab Schedule Details, 1939 Oct 42 (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - Plot Plan and Services, 1939 Aug 17 (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - Alteratiions to Steam Mains and Sewer, 1939 Aug 10 (Box 13, Folder 44)
  - Basement and Foundation Plumbing Heating and Ventilation Plans, 1939 Nov 10 (Box 13, Folder 45)
  - First Floor Plan and Details Plumbing Heating and Ventilating Plans, 1939 Nov 10 (Box 13, Folder 46)
  - Second Floor Plan and Riser Diagrams Plumbing Heating and Ventilating Plans, 1939 Nov 10 (Box 13, Folder 47)
  - Third Floor Plan and Riser Diagram Plumbing Heating and Ventilating Plans, 1939 Nov 10 (Box 13, Folder 48)
  - 4th, 9th, 10th 11th Floor Plans Details Plumbing Heating and Ventilating Plans, 1939 Nov 10 (Box 13, Folder 49)
  - 12 16th Floor Plans Details Plumbing Heating and Ventilating Plans, 1939 Nov 10 (Box 13, Folder 50)
  - Machinery Room Details Plumbing Heating and Ventilating Plans, 1939 Nov 10 (Box 13, Folder 51)
  - Duct Shaft Details Main Steam Riser Plumbing Heating and Ventilating Plans, 1939 Nov 10 (Box 13, Folder 52)
  - Plot Plan and Services, 1939 Aug 17 (Box 13, Folder 53)
  - Basement Electrical Equipment Plans, 1939 Oct 09 (Box 13, Folder 54)
  - First Floor Electrical Equipment Plans, 1939 Oct 09 (Box 13, Folder 55)
  - Second Floor Electrical Equipment Plans, 1939 Oct 09 (Box 13, Folder 56)
  - Third Floor Electrical Equipment Plans, 1939 Oct 09 (Box 13, Folder 57)
  - 5th, 9th, 10th 11th Floors Electrical Equipment Plans, 1939 Oct 09 (Box 13, Folder 58)
  - 12 16 Floors Electrical Equipment Plans, 1939 Oct 09 (Box 13, Folder 59)
  - Stairway Elevations and Diagrams Electrical Equipment Plans, 1939 Oct 09 (Box 13, Folder 60)
  - Hoover Library on War Structural Steel Column Schedule, General Notes Typical Details, 1939 Oct 27 (Box 13, Folder 61)
  - Hoover Library on War Structural Steel First Floor Framing, 1939 Oct 27 (Box 13, Folder 62)
  - Hoover Library on War Structural Steel 2nd 3rd Floor and Cubicle Roof Framing, 1939 Oct 27 (Box 13, Folder 63)
  - Hoover Library on War Structural Steel 4th to 16th Floors Incl. Dome Deck Framing, 1939 Oct 27 (Box 13, Folder 64)
  - Hoover Library on War Structural Steel Bracing Diagram Details, 1939 Oct 27 (Box 13, Folder 65)
  - Hoover Library on War Structural Steel Bracing Diagram Details, 1939 Oct 27 (Box 13, Folder 66)
  - Hoover Library on War Foundation Plan, 1939 Oct 27 (Box 13, Folder 67)
  - Tower Footing Top Reinforcement, 1939 Oct 28 (Box 13, Folder 68)
  - Tower Footing Bottom Reinforcement, 1939 Oct 29 (Box 13, Folder 69)
  - Tower Footing Sections Details, 1939 Oct 30 (Box 13, Folder 70)
  - Concrete Details Sections 1 to 5 incl., 1939 Oct 31 (Box 13, Folder 71)
  - Concrete Details Sections 6 to 8 B incl., 1939 Oct 32 (Box 13, Folder 72)
  - Concrete Details Sections 9 to 13D incl., 1939 Oct 33 (Box 13, Folder 73)
  - Concrete Details Sections 14 to 17B, 1939 Oct 34 (Box 13, Folder 74)
  - Concrete Details Sections 18 to 25 incl., 1939 Oct 35 (Box 13, Folder 75)
  - Concrete Details Sections 26 to 31 incl., 1939 Oct 36 (Box 13, Folder 76)
  - Concrete Details Sections 32, 33, 1939 Oct 37 (Box 13, Folder 77)
  - Concrete Details Sections 34, 35, 1939 Oct 38 (Box 13, Folder 78)
  - Concrete Details Stair No.1, 1939 Oct 39 (Box 13, Folder 79)
  - General Notes Slab Schedule Details, 1939 Oct 40 (Box 13, Folder 80)
  - Hoover Library Temperatures (1 of 2) (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Hoover Library Temperatures (2 of 2) (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Basement and Foundation Plumbing Heating and Ventilation Plans for Hoover Library, 1935 Nov 10 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Alterations to Steam Mains and Sewer of Hoover Library, 1939 Aug 10 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - First Floor Plan and Details Plumbing Heating and Ventilation Plans for Hoover Library, 1939 Nov 10 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Second Floor Plan and Riser Diagrams Plumbing Heating and Ventilating Plans for Hoover Library, 1939 Nov 10 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Third Floor Plan and Riser Diagram Plumbing Heating and Ventilating Plans for Hoover Library, 1939 Nov 10 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - 4th, 9th, 10th, 11th Floor Plans Details Plumbing Heating and Ventilating Plans for Hoover Library (1 of 2), 1939 Nov 10 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - 4th, 9th, 10th, 11th Floor Plans Details Plumbing Heating and Ventilating Plans for Hoover Library (2 of 2), 1939 Nov 10 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - 12th, 13th, 14th, 15th, 16th Floor Plans Details Plumbing Heating and Ventilating Plans for Hoover Library, 1939 Nov 10 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Duct Shaft Details Main Steam Riser Plumbing Heating and Ventilating Plans for Hoover Library, 1939 Nov 10 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Basement and Foundation Plumbing Heating and Ventilation Plans for Hoover Library, 1939 Nov 10 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Alterations to Steam Mains and Sewer of Hoover Library, 1939 Aug 10 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - First Floor Plan and Details Plumbing Heating and Ventilation Plans for Hoover Library, 1939 Nov 10 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Second Floor Plan and Riser Diagrams Plumbing Heating and Ventilating Plans for Hoover Library, 1939 Nov 10 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Third Floor Plan and Riser Diagram Plumbing Heating and Ventilating Plans for Hoover Library, 1939 Nov 10 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - 4th, 9th, 10th, 11th Floor Plans Details Plumbing Heating and Ventilating Plans for Hoover Library, 1939 Nov 10 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - 4th, 9th, 10th, 11th Floor Plans Details Plumbing Heating and Ventilating Plans for Hoover Library, 1939 Nov 10 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - 12th, 13th, 14th, 15th, 16th Floor Plans Details Plumbing Heating and Ventilating Plans for Hoover Library, 1939 Nov 10 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - 12th, 13th, 14th, 15th, 16th Floor Plans Details Plumbing Heating and Ventilating Plans for Hoover Library, 1939 Nov 10 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Machinery Room Details Plumbing Heating and Ventilating Plans for Hoover Library, 1939 Nov 10 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Machinery Room Details Plumbing Heating and Ventilating Plans for Hoover Library, 1939 Nov 10 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Duct Shaft Details Main Steam Riser Plumbing Heating and Ventilating Plans for Hoover Library, 1939 Nov 10 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Pilot Plan, 1939 Aug 08 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Floor Plans First Basement, 1939 Aug 08 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Floor Plans 2nd, 12th, 13th, 14th, 15th 16th, 1939 Aug 08 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Floor Plans 3rd, 4th, 9th, 10th 11th, 1939 Aug 08 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - North Elevation, 1939 Aug 08 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - South Elevation, 1939 Aug 08 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - West Elevation, 1939 Aug 08 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Section on L, 1939 Aug 08 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Main Entrance Details, 1939 Aug 08 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Spandrel Sects. 1st 12th Floors, 1939 Aug 08 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Exterior Details 14th Floor, 1939 Aug 08 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Dome Lantern, 1939 Aug 08 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - 1st Floor Details Plans Elevation, 1939 Aug 08 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Details of Lobby Exhibition Room, 1939 Aug 08 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Book Stacks, 1939 Aug 08 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Special Trim 11th Floor, 1939 Aug 08 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Toilet Room Details, 1939 Aug 08 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Stair No. 1 Stair Details, 1939 Aug 08 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Stair No. 2, 3 4, 1939 Aug 08 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Door Window Details, 1939 Aug 08 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Schedule of Finishes Detail of Lamps Standard, 1939 Aug 08 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Pilot Plan, 1939 Aug 08 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Floor Plans First Basement, 1939 Aug 08 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Floor Plans 2nd, 12th, 13th, 14th, 15th 16th, 1939 Aug 08 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Floor Plans 3rd, 4th, 9th, 10th 11th, 1939 Aug 08 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - North Elevation, 1939 Aug 08 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - South Elevation, 1939 Aug 08 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - West Elevation, 1939 Aug 08 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Section on L, 1939 Aug 08 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Main Entrance Details, 1939 Aug 08 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Spandrel Sects. 1st 12th Floors, 1939 Aug 08 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Exterior Details 14th Floor, 1939 Aug 08 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Dome Lantern, 1939 Aug 08 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - 1st Floor Details Plans Elevation, 1939 Aug 08 (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Details of Lobby Exhibition Room, 1939 Aug 08 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Book Stacks, 1939 Aug 08 (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - Special Trim 11th Floor, 1939 Aug 08 (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - Toilet Room Details, 1939 Aug 08 (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - Stair No. 1 Stair Details, 1939 Aug 08 (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - Stair No. 2, 3 4, 1939 Aug 08 (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - Door Window Details, 1939 Aug 08 (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - Schedule of Finishes Detail of Lamps Standard, 1939 Aug 08 (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - SU Hospital Foundation Plan (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - SU Hospital Foundation Sections (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - SU Hospital Foundation Sections (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - SU Hospital Foundation Sections (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - SU Hospital Elevations of Bracing Walls (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - SU Hospital Column Schedule and Details (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - SU Hospital Basement Framing Slab Schedule (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - SU Hospital Typical Floor Framing 1st to 5th Inclusive (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - SU Hospital 6th Floor Framing (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - SU Hospital Framing for Roof of North Wing / Solarium Roof / Pent House Roof (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - SU Hospital Alterations to Present Buildg. (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - SU Hospital Alterations to Present Buildg. (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - SU Hospital Sub Basement Plan (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - SU Hospital Basement Plan (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - SU Hospital First Floor Plan (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - SU Hospital Typical Floor Plan (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - SU Hospital Sixth Floor Plan (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - SU Hospital Typical Single Bed Room (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - SU Hospital Roof Plan Showing Elevator Machinery Room Floor (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - SU Hospital Sacramento Street Elevation (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - SU Hospital Section Through Court Showing West Elevation of South Wing (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - SU Hospital Spandrel Sections (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - SU Hospital Solarium #602 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - SU Hospital Detail Sheet Stairs and Elevators (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Hoover Library Alterations to Steam Mains and Sewer, 1939 Aug 10 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Hoover Library Plot Plan and Services, 42964 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Basement and Foundations Plumbing Heating and Ventilating Plans (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - First Floor Plan and Details Plumbing Heating and Ventilating Plans (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Second Floor Plan and Riser Diagrams Plubming Heating and Ventilating Plans (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Third Floor Plan and Riser Diagram Plubming Heating and Ventilating Plans (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - 4th, 9th, 10th 11th Floor Plans Plumbing Heating and Ventilating Plans (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - 12th, 13th, 14th, 15th, 16th Floor Plans Details Plumbing Heating and Ventilating Plans (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Machinery Room Details Plumbing Heating and Ventilating Plans (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Basement Electrical Equipment Plans (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - First Floor Electrical Equipment Plans (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Second Floor Electrical Equipment Plans (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Third Floor Electrical Equipment Plans (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - 5th, 9th, 10th 11th Floors Electrical Equipment Plans (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - 12 16 Floors Electrical Equipment Plans (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Stairway Elevations and Diagrams Electrical Equipment Plans (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Hoover Library on War Plot Plan, 1939 Aug 08 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Hoover Library on War Floor Plans First Basement, 1939 Nov 06 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Hoover Library on War Floor Plans First Basement, 1940 Apr 03 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Hoover Library on War Floor Plans 2nd, 12th, 13th, 14th, 15th 16th, 1939 Aug 08 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Hoover Library on War Floor Plans 2nd, 12th, 13th, 14th, 15th 16th, 1940 Apr 03 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Hoover Library on War Floor Plans 3rd, 4th, 9th, 10th 11th, 1939 Aug 08 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Hoover Library on War North Elevation, 1939 Aug 09 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Hoover Library on War South Elevation, 1939 Aug 10 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Hoover Library on War West Elevation, 1939 Aug 11 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Hoover Library on War Section on L, 1939 Aug 12 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Hoover Library Main Entrance Details, 1939 Aug 13 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Hoover Library on War Spandrel Sects. 1st 12th Floors, 1939 Aug 14 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Hoover Library on War Exterior Details 14th Floor, 1939 Aug 15 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Hoover Library on War Dome Lantern, 1939 Aug 16 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Hoover Library on War 1st Floor Details Plans Elevations, 1939 Aug 17 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Hoover Library on War Details of Lobby Exhibition Room, 1939 Aug 18 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Hoover Library on War Book Stacks, 1939 Aug 19 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Hoover Library on War Special Trim 11th Floor, 1939 Aug 20 (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - Hoover Library on War Revised 11th Floor Plan Special Trim, 1940 Apr 03 (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Hoover Library on War Revised 11th Floor Plan Special Trim, 1940 Jun 24 (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - Hoover Library on War Toilet Room Details, 1939 Aug 08 (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - Hoover Library on War Stair No.1 Stair Details, 1939 Aug 09 (Box 17, Folder 38)
  - Hoover Library on War Stair No. 2, 3 4 Stair Details, 1939 Aug 10 (Box 17, Folder 39)
  - Hoover Library on War Door Window Details, 1939 Aug 11 (Box 17, Folder 40)
  - Hoover Library on War Revised Vaulting Dome Details for Lobby, 1939 Aug 12 (Box 17, Folder 41)
  - Hoover Library on War Structural Steel Column Schedule, General Notes Typical Details, 1939 Oct 27 (Box 17, Folder 42)
  - Hoover Library on War Structural Steel First Floor Framing, 1939 Oct 27 (Box 17, Folder 43)
  - Hoover Library on War Structural Steel 2nd 3rd Floor and Cubicle Roof Framing, 1939 Oct 27 (Box 17, Folder 44)
  - Hoover Library on War Structural Steel 4th to 16th Floors Incl. Dome Deck Framing, 1939 Oct 27 (Box 17, Folder 45)
  - Hoover Library on War Structural Steel Bracing Diagram Details, 1939 Oct 27 (Box 17, Folder 46)
  - Hoover Library on War Structural Steel Bracing Diagram Details, 1939 Oct 27 (Box 17, Folder 47)
  - Hoover Library on War Foundation Plan, 1939 Oct 27 (Box 17, Folder 48)
  - Tower Footing Top Reinforcement, 1939 Oct 28 (Box 17, Folder 49)
  - Tower Footing Bottom Reinforcement, 1939 Oct 29 (Box 17, Folder 50)
  - Tower Footing Sections Details, 1939 Oct 30 (Box 17, Folder 51)
  - Concrete Details Sections 1 to 5 incl., 1939 Oct 31 (Box 17, Folder 52)
  - Concrete Details Sections 6 to 8 B incl., 1939 Oct 32 (Box 17, Folder 53)
  - Concrete Details Sections 9 to 13D incl., 1939 Oct 33 (Box 17, Folder 54)
  - Concrete Details Sections 14 to 17B, 1939 Oct 34 (Box 17, Folder 55)
  - Concrete Details Sections 18 to 25 incl., 1939 Oct 35 (Box 17, Folder 56)
  - Concrete Details Sections 26 to 31 incl., 1939 Oct 36 (Box 17, Folder 57)
  - Concrete Details Sections 32, 33, 1939 Oct 37 (Box 17, Folder 58)
  - Concrete Details Sections 34, 35, 1939 Oct 38 (Box 17, Folder 59)
  - Concrete Details Stair No.1, 1939 Oct 39 (Box 17, Folder 60)